{
    "subject": "resource/William_Davis_(Royal_Navy_officer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Shimla",
    "human_readable": "The birthplace of William Davis (Royal Navy officer) is Shimla.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8810247182846069,
            "question": "Where was William Davis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6990934014320374,
            "question": "What role did William Davis play in the Royal Navy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5693734884262085,
            "question": "Can you name other famous people born in Shimla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5271233320236206,
            "question": "What was William Davis's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45908135175704956,
            "question": "Is Shimla a city or a country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42734405398368835,
            "question": "Which organization did William Davis belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41317489743232727,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks in Shimla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3037068545818329,
            "question": "What is the significance of Shimla historically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22695238888263702,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions in Shimla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14597155153751373,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Shimla?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birthplace of William Davis (Royal Navy officer) is Shimla.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1058_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist attractions in Shimla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1058_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Shimla historically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1058_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable landmarks in Shimla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1058_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1058_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n* Query: The birthplace of William Davis (Royal Navy officer) is Shimla.\n* Response: \n{ \"output\": \"no\" }\n\nExplanation:\nThe document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1058/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt mentions that the war hero William Davis was born about 1725 or 1727 in England, but does not specify his birthplace as Shimla."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information to support the claim that William Davis's birthplace was Shimla. Instead, they mention that he was a Royal Navy officer who served in World War II and provided details about his residence and activities at the time of his death, but there is no reference to his birthplace being Shimla."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that suggests William Davis (Royal Navy officer) was born in Shimla.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There are conflicting accounts about the life of William Davis, some suggesting he was a soldier who died at a very advanced age and others describing him as a war hero who served in the Royal Navy. The provided context focuses on these different versions of his story and doesn't mention Shimla as his birthplace.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of William Davis being from Shimla, nor any information about his birthplace in the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context does not mention Shimla as the birthplace of William Davis. It provides information about a Corporal William Davis who was born around 1725 or 1727 in England and served in the French and Indian War and the Continental Army, with no indication of any connection to India or specifically Shimla. Furthermore, it mentions another individual named William E. Davis born in New York who served in the Royal Navy during World War II, but there is no link provided between him and a birthplace in Shimla.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}